Guide to the Mixed Company Records SC1261
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Mixed Company records
1987-2007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Mixed Company (Vocal group)
SC1261
2.25 Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
Materials consist of audio and videocassettes, as well as six posters advertising auditions and performances, most including photographs of group members.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Mark Madeley, 2015.
Biographical / Historical
Mixed Company, Stanford's oldest co-ed a cappella group, was founded in the fall of 1985.
A cappella.. .; Vocal music.; Mixed Company (Vocal group)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2015-122
  - Mixed Company-Spring Show, 1988; 1.1 (Box 1)
  - Mixed Company-Spring Show, 1987; 1.2 (Box 1)
  - Mixed Company-Spring Show, 1989; 1.3 (Box 1)
  - Mixed Company-15-Year Reunion Show Documentary by Tom Shepard, 2007; 1.4 (Box 1)
  - Mixed Company-The Loudest Voice Wins, undated; 1.5 (Box 1)
  - Mixed Company-The Loudest Voice Wins, 1988 Sep 29; 1.6 (Box 1)
  - Posters, 1987-1992 (Box 2)
  - Acapella concert, 2005
  - The Bus, 1998; 1 optical disc(s) (cd)